<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Nasdaq Company Profile.  Randomly genenrated. -->
<!DOCTYPE Companies SYSTEM "profile.dtd">
<Companies>
<Company><Symbol>PLRX</Symbol><Name></Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>47616</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TDDD</Symbol><Name>3Dlabs Inc., Ltd.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$56.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>80062</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Supplies high-performance, cost-effective graphics semiconductors, software and related technology designed to bring workstation-class 3d graphics to the personal computer. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>THDO</Symbol><Name>3DO Company (The)</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$361.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>73025</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which develop, publish and market interactive entertainment products for multiple computer platforms; And design and license hardware technologies for the 64-bit consumer and pc markets.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ACMR</Symbol><Name>A.C. Moore Arts &amp; Crafts, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$34.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>48577</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiary which operates arts and crafts superstores which offer vast assortment of traditional and contemporary arts and crafts merchandise for a wide range of customers. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ACSEF</Symbol><Name>A.C.S. Electronics Limited</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$3.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>55084</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops and produces fully-digital motion control products utilized in advanced industrial application, medical scanning and imaging systems, semi-conductor manufacturing equipment, electronic testing and inspection stations and high-quality printing machinery.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ABCB</Symbol><Name>ABC Bancorp</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$93.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>24498</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking operations, credit card services, trust services, investment banking services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ABTE</Symbol><Name>Able Telcom Holding Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$109.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>57277</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide specialized communication services including installation and maintenance of telephone central office switching equipment, coaxial and fiber optic cable and wireless networks; Maintain and install electric utility grids and water and sewer utilities; And provide specialty products and services relating to traffic management systems including manufacture, installation and maintenance of highway signage, lighting and guardrailing.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ABRI</Symbol><Name>Abrams Industries, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$12.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>58859</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which construct, expand and remodel retail store buildings, warehouses, banks and shopping centers; Manufacture and sell store fixtures; Design and produce point-of-purchase display units; And conduct real estate development operations.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ACLY</Symbol><Name>Accelr8 Technology Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$12.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>79667</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops and markets proprietary software products which function as bridge between unix and vax computing environments; And provides consulting services for year 2000 compliance.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>AABC</Symbol><Name>Access Anytime Bancorp, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$10.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>9057</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operations, mortgage banking services, credit card services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>AWWC</Symbol><Name>Access Worldwide Communications, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$12.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>46340</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides outsourced marketing services consisting of marketing, sales and customer service programs such as market research, database analysis, telesales/services, direct mail, sales territory management, product sampling and fulfillment, which assist large companies in penetrating complex and hard-to-reach market segments.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ACEC</Symbol><Name>ACE*COMM Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$33.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>49965</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and services operations support system products for networks deployed by telecommunications service providers such as telephone companies, other public carriers and large enterprises operating data and voice networks using intranet and the internet.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ACME</Symbol><Name>ACME Communications, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>77963</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiary which owns and operates broadcast television stations.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ADEX</Symbol><Name>ADE Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$201.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>75502</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures, markets and services metrology and inspection systems used in semiconductor wafer manufacturing and the fabrication of integrated circuits and in testing computer disks and disk drives. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ADFC</Symbol><Name>AdForce, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$500.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>89153</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Provides centralized, outsourced ad management and delivery services on the internet, including campaign design, inventory management, targeting, ad delivery, tracking, measuring and reporting capabilities.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ADBE</Symbol><Name>Adobe Systems Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$7,209.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>70630</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops and markets systems and application software which enables users to work with professional creative tools, assemble illustrations, images and text into fully formatted documents, output documents directly to any kind of printing device, and distribute documents on paper, video or compact disc, over an e-mail system, corporate network, on-line service, or the internet.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ADVNB</Symbol><Name>ADVANTA Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$340.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>59204</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which market, issue and service gold and standard business </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>AIRM</Symbol><Name>Air Methods Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$23.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>15894</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Provides aeromedical emergency transport services; And designs, manufactures and installs medical aircraft interiors and other aerospace products, such as modular, multi-functional interiors, multi-mission interiors and medical suites for fixed wing aircraft.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ALCD</Symbol><Name>Alcide Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$32.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>71414</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Researches, develops and commercializes various cleaning products such as animal health products, dairy line products, hard surface sterilants and disinfectants and air conditioning system disinfectant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ALGO</Symbol><Name>Algos Pharmaceutical Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$161.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>45388</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Develops pain management products, including narcotic drugs such as morphine, hydrocodone and oxycodone, and non-narcotic analgesics such as acetaminophen and ibuprofen. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ALCO</Symbol><Name>Alico, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$106.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>26239</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Produces and markets citrus fruits; Produces beef cattle; Harvests sugarcane; Owns timberlands; Rents real estate for grazing, farming and recreation uses; Leases oil and mineral properties; And mines rock, sand, baserock and other road building and construction materials.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ALLY</Symbol><Name>Alliance Gaming Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$79.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>68702</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which design, manufacture and distribute electronic gaming machines; Design, assemble and sell computerized monitoring systems for slot and video gaming machines which provide casino operators with on-line real time accounting, security, maintenance and player tracking capabilities; And own and operate casino.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>AHAA</Symbol><Name>Alpha Industries, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,118.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>42220</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures, and markets microwave semiconductor devices, components, subsystems and microwave ferrite and other microwave ceramic materials. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ALTR</Symbol><Name>Altera Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$9,429.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>46603</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops and markets complementary-metal-oxide-silicon programmable logic integrated circuits and associated computer-aided engineering development systems, and erasable programmable logic devices which customers configure for a specific end-use application using proprietary software.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>AHCI</Symbol><Name>Ambanc Holding Co., Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$83.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>98525</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operations, mortgage banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>AALA</Symbol><Name>AmerAlia, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$20.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>34990</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Owns naturally-occurring, deposit of sodium bicarbonate in colorado; And recovers, produces and sells sodium bicarbonate and related products.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ACHIW</Symbol><Name>American Country Holdings Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>37099</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>AMEP</Symbol><Name>American Educational Products, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$11.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>58709</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Manufactures and markets hands-on educational materials, multi-media and science products and maps for students, teachers, and parents. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ANFI</Symbol><Name>American National Financial, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$17.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>61850</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide title insurance services as well as other real estate related financial and informational services, including escrow, real estate information, trustee sale guarantees and appraisals. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ASYS</Symbol><Name>Amtech Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$4.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>33036</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which manufacture and market wafer processing and handling equipment for semiconductor manufacturers. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ANCO</Symbol><Name>ANACOMP, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$234.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>19636</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides digital document-management outsouce services, field maintenance services and document-management systems and supplies. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ANLG</Symbol><Name>Analogy, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$19.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>92007</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and supports software and model libraries for top down design and behavioral simulation of mixed digital and analog signals and technology systems; And provides maintenance and support services for its systems.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ANCR</Symbol><Name>Ancor Communications, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$632.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>38236</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures and markets fibre channel communications network products, including switches and application specific integrated circuits. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ANTC</Symbol><Name>ANTEC Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$2,029.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>19800</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures and supplies optical transmission, construction, rebuild and maintenance equipment for the broadband communications industry; And provides material management services, including procurement, storage, shipping, tracking and reporting of product deployment.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ARSD</Symbol><Name>Arabian Shield Development Company</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$23.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>2219</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which own and operate a specialty products refinery in the united states; And develop various mineral properties, primarily zinc, copper, silver and gold properties, in suadi arabia.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ARWM</Symbol><Name>Arrow-Magnolia International, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$10.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>95273</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Manufactures and distributes specialty chemical products, including aircraft coatings, corrosion preventatives, construction chemicals such as release agent and concrete strippers and telecommunication formulations such as cale cleaners and fiber optic lubricants, for cleaning ana maintaining equipment, as well as for general maintenance and sanitation; And distributes nonchemical poducts including mops, brooms, paper products and poly liners.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ATSN</Symbol><Name>Artesyn Technologies, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$752.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>98396</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, manufactures and sells power conversion products for electronic equipment used in commercial and industrial applications, automation hardware and software systems and components used in process control and data acquisition applications, and high performance single-boad computers and systems for real time applications; And provides repair services for a variety of products primarily manufactured by </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ALIF</Symbol><Name>Artificial Life</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$130.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>73722</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and supports software programs which automate and simplify time-consuming and complex business-related internet functions, such as web navigation, direct marketing, user profiling, information gathering, messaging, knowledge management, sales response and call center automation; And provides software consulting services to corporations and other entities seeking software solutions.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ASTSF</Symbol><Name>ASE Test, Limited</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$2,022.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>59339</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ASEC</Symbol><Name>Aseco Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$10.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>8744</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and markets test handlers used to automate the testing of integrated circuits in surface mount packages. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ASTNW</Symbol><Name>Ashton Technology Group, Inc. (The)</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$7.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>900</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ATLCW</Symbol><Name>Atlantic Pharmaceuticals, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>10280</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>AUBN</Symbol><Name>Auburn National Bancorporation, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$60.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>10355</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiary which performs commercial banking operations, mortgage banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ADBL</Symbol><Name>Audible, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$78.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>14815</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides internet-delivered premium spoken audio content for playback on personal computers and mobile devices.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ABSC</Symbol><Name>Aurora Biosciences Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$261.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>23425</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Designs and develops proprietary drug discovery systems, services and technologies to accelerate and enhance the discovery of new medicines. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ASPX</Symbol><Name>Auspex Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$227.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>488</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures, distributes and supports a line of unix/nfs file servers to enhance the performance of large multivendor client/server networks. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>AVDOP</Symbol><Name>Avado Brands Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$67.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>91594</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>AVIIZ</Symbol><Name>AVI BioPharma, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>88988</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>AWRE</Symbol><Name>Aware, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$597.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>82500</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops and markets telecommunications software, chipsets and modems which increase the speed of data communications over conventional copper telephone lines. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>AXHM</Symbol><Name>Axiohm Transaction Solutions Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$4.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>35751</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and distributes transaction printers and mechanisms, impact printheads, bar code printers, and related services and supplies such as labels and ribbons; Manufactures and markets magnetic read and write heads and modules for credit card and debit card readers, check readers and airline ticket readers; And offers printhead repair and services.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BYBI</Symbol><Name>Back Yard Burgers, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$8.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>95192</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Operates and franchises quick-service, predominantly drive-thru restaurants under the name </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BFOH</Symbol><Name>BancFirst Ohio Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$168.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>44613</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking operations, mortgage banking, investment banking services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BKCT</Symbol><Name>Bancorp Connecticut Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$84.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>34478</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>One-bank holding company with subsidiary which performs commerical banking operations and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BSXT</Symbol><Name>Bank of Essex</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$17.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>23718</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Performs commercial banking operations and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>OZRK</Symbol><Name>Bank of the Ozarks</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$64.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>29979</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking operations, mortgage banking, trust services, insurance services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BNKU</Symbol><Name>Bank United Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,139.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>75328</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Bank and savings and loan holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking operations, savings bank operations, mortgage banking and other related financial services. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BANC</Symbol><Name>BankAtlantic Bancorp, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$222.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>18332</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operations, investment banking services, leasing and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BELFB</Symbol><Name>Bel Fuse Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$161.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>23292</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and sells electronic components, such as delay lines, miniature and micro fuses, inductive components and hybrid circuits, and transformers used in local area networking, telecommunications, automotive and consumer electronic applications.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BERK</Symbol><Name>Berkshire Energy Resources</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$62.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>72596</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiary which distribute and sell natural gas for residential, commercial and industrial use; Market liquified petroleum gas; And lease and sell gas burning equipment.  new registrant.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BIGE</Symbol><Name>Big Entertainment, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$147.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>69431</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Owns and licenses rights to certain original characters and concepts created by best-selling authors and media celebrities; Publishes and distributes illustrated novels; And retails variety of entertainment products and merchandise through kiosks and an on-line store.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BCHE</Symbol><Name>Biochem Pharma Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$2,702.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>14523</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Researches, develops and markets therapeutic, vaccine and diagnostic products for the prevention, detection and treatment of infectious and other diseases. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RINO</Symbol><Name>Blue Rhino Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$51.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>30876</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Provides consumers with a convenient means to exchange empty grill cylinders for clean, safer, precision-filled cylinders. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BRBI</Symbol><Name>Blue River Bancshares, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$6.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>21696</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operations and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BCII</Symbol><Name>Bone Care International, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$95.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>80097</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Discovers, develops and commercializes d-hormones for treatment of hyperparathyroidism associated with end-stage renal disease, renal osteodystrophy, osteoporosis, psoriasis, prostate and breast cancer. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BLPG</Symbol><Name>Boron, LePore &amp; Associates, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$73.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>40956</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides outsourced promotional, marketing, educational and field sales force logistics services to the pharmaceutical industry. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BOYD</Symbol><Name>Boyd Bros. Transportation Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$30.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>12334</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Provides flatbed truckload carrier services, primarily hauling steel products and building materials on time-definite delivery basis. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BRKL</Symbol><Name>Brookline Bancorp, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$294.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>15233</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operations, mortgage banking services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BOSS</Symbol><Name>Building One Services Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$521.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>51145</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Offers a broad range of mechanical and electrical installation, maintenance and specialty services and janitorial and maintenance management services. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BMLS</Symbol><Name>Burke Mills, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$5.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>69016</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Twists, textures, winds, dyes, and processes filament, novelty and spun yarn; And dyes and processes yarn on a commission basis.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CCBL</Symbol><Name>C-COR.net Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$338.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>89237</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs and manufactures electronic equipment for use in cable television distribution systems and data transmission systems, such as trunk, bridging, distributing and line extender amplifiers, status monitor systems, single and dual cable lan amplifiers and video surveillance systems; And provides full line of technical customer services including network analysis, design, installation, training and maintenance.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CHRW</Symbol><Name>C.H. Robinson Worldwide, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,377.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>49486</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides multimodal transportation services and logistics solutions, such as raw materials sourcing, freight consolidation, cross-docking and contract warehousing. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CPCL</Symbol><Name>C.P. Clare Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$55.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>77008</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and sells high voltage analog semiconductor integrated packages and discrete components, electromagnetic relays and switches, surge protection devices, transformers and specialized electronic components used in a variety of applications, including telephone network interfaces caller identification uses, high current mofset switching, integrated packages testers, high frequency communications, scanners and radio frequency equipments.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CLCI</Symbol><Name>Cadiz, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$308.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>92930</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Acquires and develops raw land, primarily in desert regions of southern california, which the company has identified as having indigenous water supplies. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CDMS</Symbol><Name>Cadmus Communications Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$103.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>17663</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides printing, publishing and graphic arts services, including periodical production, promotional and financial printing, and direct marketing services; Offers specialty packaging and point-of-purchase product lines and other products and services; And develops customized software to help clients meet their own specific marketing challenges and goals.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CLBR</Symbol><Name>Caliber Learning Network, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$23.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>33261</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Provides educational and training programs in the fields of health care, management development, information technology/engineering and education. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CANDE</Symbol><Name>Candie's, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$54.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>31794</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, markets, imports and distributes women's and girl's leisure and fashion footwear and handbags, children's footwear as well as men's workboots, hiking boots, winter boots and casual shoes; Licenses the candie's (r) trademark to third parties; And operates retail, outlets and specialty stores.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CNDL</Symbol><Name>Candlewood Hotel Company, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$17.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>36115</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Develops, owns, operates and franchises extended-stay hotels. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CBEVW</Symbol><Name>Capital Beverage Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>54700</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CRDM</Symbol><Name>Cardima, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$19.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>33655</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, manufactures and markets minimally invasive, single-use, microcatheter-based systems for mapping and ablation of atrial fibrillation and ventricular tachycardia utilizing electrical signals and radiofrequency energy. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CARY</Symbol><Name>Carey International, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$220.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>34936</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Owns and operates chauffeured vehicle services utilizing sedans, limousines, vans and minibuses to provide services for airport pick-ups and drop-offs, promotions, special events and leisure travel worldwide; Licenses </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CRZO</Symbol><Name>Carrizo Oil &amp; Gas, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$20.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>14584</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Explores for, develops and produces natural gas and crude oil. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CASCW</Symbol><Name>Casco International Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>36434</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CATT</Symbol><Name>Catapult Communicatons Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$203.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>33461</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures, markets and supports an advanced software-based test system offering an integrated suite of testing applications for the global telecommunications industry.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CLTK</Symbol><Name>Celeritek, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$42.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>4869</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and markets high-frequency transceiver products  which perform core transmit and receive functions for wireless communications systems. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CTIC</Symbol><Name>Cell Therapeutics, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$38.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>32048</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Discovers, develops and markets small molecule drugs based on proprietary technology for treatment of cancer, and inflammatory and immune diseases. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CENT</Symbol><Name>Central Garden &amp; Pet Company</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$207.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>76930</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Distributes lawn, garden, pet and pool supply products. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CEPH</Symbol><Name>Cephalon, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$513.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>71586</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Discovers, develops and markets therapeutic products for treating neurodegenerative diseases, such as alzheimer's disease and head and spinal injuries. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CERN</Symbol><Name>Cerner Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$512.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>29217</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, markets, installs and supports member/patient-focused clinical and management information systems designed to automate the process of healthcare by accumulating data on care provided to members/patients, maintaining such data in a database repository and providing access to such data for users of clinical information.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CFWC</Symbol><Name>CFW Communications Company</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$299.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>64358</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide telephone and related communications services and equipment to businesses and residential customers; And own and operate wireless and wireline television systems.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CHMP</Symbol><Name>Champion Industries, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$54.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>802</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides commercial printing, including printing of business cards, letterhead, envelopes and color brochures; And distributes office products and furniture such as file folders, pencils, computer paper, laser cartridges, desks, chairs, file cabinets and computer furniture.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CRAI</Symbol><Name>Charles River Associates Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$241.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>38655</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Performs economic and business consulting, applying advanced analytic techniques and in-depth industry knowledge to complex engagements for a broad range of clients. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CXILW</Symbol><Name>Chem International, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>27056</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CFCM</Symbol><Name>Chief Consolidated Mining Company</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$24.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>43014</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Owns and develops patented and unpatented mining properties. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>KIDS</Symbol><Name>Childrens Comprehensive Services Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$51.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>55770</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides education, treatment and juvenile justice services for at risk and troubled youth; And provides management services to residential treatment facilities.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PHONW</Symbol><Name>ChoiceTel Communications, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>28393</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CHMD</Symbol><Name>Chronimed Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$95.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>9475</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and distributes pharmaceuticals, general medical products and patient educational materials and products directly to the individual and to the patients of managed care and case management companies nationwide, as well as institutions which serve these patients.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CIMA</Symbol><Name>CIMA LABS INC.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$65.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>93190</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops and markets </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CINF</Symbol><Name>Cincinnati Financial Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$6,062.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>21992</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which underwrite fire, automobile, casualty and other related forms of insurance; Lease and finance automobiles, trucks, computers, construction equipment and office equipment; Owns certain real estate in the greater cincinnati area; And intends to offer investment management services to corporations, institutions, and high net worth individuals.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CNRM</Symbol><Name>Cinram International Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$505.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>84219</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Manufactures audio cds, cd-rom, and pre-recorded audio and video cassette tapes. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CTXS</Symbol><Name>Citrix Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$5,732.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>27107</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Supplies multi-user application server products which enable the effective and efficient enterprise-wide deployment of applications designed for </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CLHB</Symbol><Name>Clean Harbors, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$14.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>76518</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide comprehensive environmental services, including resource recovery, transportation, storage and treatment of industrial waste; And provide analytical testing, technical and consulting and information management services.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CLSR</Symbol><Name>CLOSURE Medical Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$183.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>74188</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Develops, commercializes and manufactures medical adhesive products used to close and seal wounds and incisions rapidly and stop leakage of blood and other bodily fluids form injured tissue. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CNET</Symbol><Name>CNET, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$4,060.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>22258</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Provides internet content and television programming such as news, product reviews, feature stories, interviews and other information about computers, the internet and digital technologies. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>COMT</Symbol><Name>Coda Music Technology, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$24.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>67896</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Develops and markets proprietary music technology products which enhance music learning and composition, increase productivity and make practicing and performing music fun. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>COLO</Symbol><Name>Colonel's International, Inc. (The)</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$151.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>91780</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which design, manufacture and distribute plastic bumpers, facias, support beams and brackets for application as replacement collision parts for domestic automobile models; Operate raceway offering sports car, stock car, motorcycle, go-kart, and road and drag races; And design and manufacture pickup truck bedliners, tailgate covers and rail kits.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CBMD</Symbol><Name>Columbia Bancorp</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$55.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>92159</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiary which performs commercial banking operations, credit card services, mortgage banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CMTO</Symbol><Name>Com21, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$288.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>17743</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, markets and sells value-added, high-speed communications solutions for the broadband access market. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CBNY</Symbol><Name>Commercial Bank of New York</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$61.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>61799</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Performs commercial banking operations, trust services and other relatand other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CNAF</Symbol><Name>Commercial National Financial Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$58.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>9248</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiary which performs commercial banking operations and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ETVC</Symbol><Name>Compu-Dawn, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$7.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>52629</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, licenses, installs and services computer software products and systems for law enforcement and public safety agencies, such as computer-aided dispatching, computer interfacing with state and national crime information databases, advanced mobile on-line radio computing, automatic vehicle location, record management and photo-image database systems; And provides internet, e-commerce and telecommunications services marketing products and services.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CSRE</Symbol><Name>Comshare, Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$28.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>37427</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and supports client/server financial analytic applications software for management planning and control; And provides consulting, training and support services to the company's customers.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CNXT</Symbol><Name>Conexant Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$7,791.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>41120</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Manufactures semiconductor integrated circuit products for a broad range of communications applications, including analog pc and fax modem chipsets. new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CNCT</Symbol><Name>Connetics Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$101.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>29905</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Researches and develops therapeutics for diseases which involve connective tissues of the body. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CPSS</Symbol><Name>Consumer Portfolio Services, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$19.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>7857</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Purchases, sells and services retail automobile installment sale contracts originated by new-car franchise dealers which sell both new and used automobiles, light trucks and passenger vans. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CMETS</Symbol><Name>Continental Mortgage and Equity Trust</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$59.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>91242</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>DIGM</Symbol><Name>Control Chief Holdings, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$4.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>97466</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiary which designs, engineers and manufactures remote control devices for material handling equipment and other industrial applications. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CPIA</Symbol><Name>CPI Aerostructures, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$3.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>79780</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Produces structural aircraft parts and sub-assemblies, including pylons, aprons, spars and lower pan assemblies for commercial and military sectors of the aircraft industry; Provides engineering, technical and program management services; And manufactures precision machine parts and sub-assemblies for the electronic industry, including computer and microwave device manufacturers, as well as materials handling, aerospace and banking industries.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CKEY</Symbol><Name>CrossKeys Systems Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$82.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>99575</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and supports telecommunications management software products and services, including element, network and service management solutions which facilitate implementation of multi-vendor network devices, allow telecommunications service provides to configure, monitor and report on network performance, and facilitate deployment and management of differentiated services.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CSPI</Symbol><Name>CSP Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$18.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>93128</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and markets high-performance, real-time computer systems, software and services, offering high-quality products, customer service and support; And provides network integration services including consulting, systems integration and outsourcing.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CMLS</Symbol><Name>Cumulus Media Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$646.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>22466</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Owns and operates fm and am radio broadcasting stations in mid-size and smaller radio markets. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CYBA</Symbol><Name>Cybear, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$122.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>82699</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops information technology, internet-based browser applications designed to improve communications and increase efficiencies for health care providers by providing information and internet-based productivity applications to the participants in the healthcare industry.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CYSP</Symbol><Name>Cybershop.com Inc</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$45.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>60752</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Offers retail products from manufacturers through its online stores on the internet and america online. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CYMI</Symbol><Name>Cymer, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,008.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>3588</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides excimer laser illumination sources for use in deep ultraviolet photolithography systems targeted at the pilot and volume production segments of the semiconductor manufacturing market. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CTII</Symbol><Name>CytoTherapeutics, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$27.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>56795</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Researches and develops novel cell therapy systems designed to deliver therapeutic substances to the central nervous system, thus effectively treating chronic pain, parkinson's disease and amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, as well as other diseases and disorders such as huntingtons disease.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>DMRK</Symbol><Name>Damark International, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$57.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>92146</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Markets quality general merchandise products, such as computers, home office, home decor, consumer electronics, home improvements and sporting and fitness goods through mail-order catalogs and membership clubs; And operates travel club which offers members discounts on hotels worldwide, airline frequent flyer miles or cash rebates, car rental discounts and upgrades, services from a full service travel agency, as well as discounts on cruises, theme park attractions, sailing, skiing and golfing vacations.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>DTLN</Symbol><Name>Data Transmission Network Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$280.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>66071</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Provides on-line agricultural market information, financial news such as quotes on stocks, bonds, mutual money market funds, and other information and communications services. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>DSCP</Symbol><Name>Datascope Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$573.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>88399</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, manufactures and markets proprietary products for clinical health care markets in interventional cardiology, anesthesiology, cardiovascular and vascular surgery and for use in emergency rooms and intensive care units. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>DATA</Symbol><Name>DataTrak International, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$24.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>85563</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Manages multi-therapeutic clinical research sites which assist third parties in conducting clinical research necessary to obtain regulatory approval for new drugs; And provide certain electronic data management services to such parties.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>DAVX</Symbol><Name>Davox Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$205.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>79459</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, produces and markets computer-aided communications systems which automate and integrate telephone and data communications functions in applications, such as collections, customer service and telemarketing. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TWDE</Symbol><Name>DECS TRUST V</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>3151</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>DECTW</Symbol><Name>Dectron International, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>86712</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>DMDSW</Symbol><Name>Dental/Medical Diagnostic Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$2.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>98581</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>DCBK</Symbol><Name>Desert Community Bank</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$26.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>85889</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Performs commercial banking operations, credit card services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>DLNK</Symbol><Name>Digital Link Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$80.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>63514</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures, markets and supports a broad range of high speed digital access products for wide area networks worldwide. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>DIIG</Symbol><Name>DII Group, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,149.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>74594</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which manufacture complex printed circuit boards using surface mount, and pin-through-hole technologies; And formerly manufactured in-circuit test software and hardware.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>DTEK</Symbol><Name>Display Technologies Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$27.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>34919</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures, distributes and services electronic signs for institutions, entertainment complexes, shopping centers and other commercial enterprises; Manufactures and sells filtration products, which substantially reduce or eliminate water and most foreign contaminants from compressed air lines; And produces graphic arts and screen printed products.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>DOCD</Symbol><Name>DOCdata N.V.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>57832</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>DOMZ</Symbol><Name>Dominguez Services Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$44.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>27352</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which produce and supply water for residential, commercial, industrial and agricultural customers. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>EWBC</Symbol><Name>East West Bancorp, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$272.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>54033</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiary which performs commercial banking operations and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>EASTW</Symbol><Name>Eastbrokers International Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>2847</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ECBE</Symbol><Name>ECB Bancorp Inc</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>94932</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiary which performs commercial banking operations, mortgage banking, credit card services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ELON</Symbol><Name>Echelon Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$244.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>36693</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and supports a family of hardware and software products and services, including integrated circuits, transceivers, intelligent routers, network interfaces, and software tools and toolkits, which enables original equipment manufacturers and systems integrators to design and implement open, interoperable, distributed control networks.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ESTI</Symbol><Name>Eclipse Surgical Technologies, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$196.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>6458</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures and markets laser based surgical products and disposable fiber-optic accessories for treatment of advanced cardiovascular disease. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ESSI</Symbol><Name>Eco Soil Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$103.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>45035</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets, supports and sells proprietary biological and traditional chemical products which provide solutions for a wide variety of turf, crop and water problems and related distribution equipment in the golf and agricultural industries. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ECSGY</Symbol><Name>ECsoft Group plc</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$131.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>94499</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide information technology consulting, applications development, systems integrations service and internet and intranet integration services, to large european-based companies and organizations. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>EDEL</Symbol><Name>Edelbrock Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$72.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>56440</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures, distributes and markets wide range of high-quality performance products, including intake manifolds, carburetors, camshafts, cylinder heads, exhaust systems and other components which enhance street, off-road, recreational and competition vehicle performance; And designs and markets products to enhance engine and vehicle appearance such as chrome and polished aluminum air cleaners, valve covers and breathers.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>EFCX</Symbol><Name>Electric Fuel Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$17.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>45092</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Researches, develops and commercializes an advanced zinc-air battery technology for electric vehicles, portable consumer electronic devices and defense applications. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GTGO</Symbol><Name>Electrocon International Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$13.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>51194</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which distribute semiconductor products primarily computer chips; And distribute golf carts, irrigation products and systems, fertilizers and turf equipment.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ELTK</Symbol><Name>Eltek Ltd.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$3.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>39857</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>EMCI</Symbol><Name>EMC Insurance Group, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$108.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>81588</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which underwrite property and casualty, nonstandard risk automobile and excess and surplus lines of insurance and reinsurance. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>EMLX</Symbol><Name>Emulex Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,742.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>92028</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and markets software and hardware based network access products including printer and network access servers and high speed fibre channel products. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>EPTG</Symbol><Name>EPL Technologies, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$9.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>43842</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures and markets food processing products which inhibit the enzymatic browning and subsequent degradation of fresh fruit and vegetables; Markets flexible packaging for uses in the snack food, bakery and confectionery industries, and for other uses; Markets fresh-cut fruits and vegetables; And provides scientific and technical services, including microbiological testing.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ESST</Symbol><Name>ESS Technology, Inc</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$563.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>2949</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, markets and supports highly integrated mixed signal semiconductor and software solutions for multimedia applications in the personal computer and consumer marketplaces, including sound cards, single audio chips, programmable single chip processors and decoder chips.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ESCCG</Symbol><Name>Evans &amp; Sutherland Computer Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>130</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>EXBT</Symbol><Name>Exabyte Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$108.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>70430</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, manufactures and markets high capacity magnetic tape subsystems and robotic tape libraries for cost-effective data storage solutions; And offers related consumables, including media cartridges, as well as cleaning cartridges and data cartidges holders.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>EXAP</Symbol><Name>Exchange Applications, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$307.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>45056</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Provides customer optimization software and solutions which enable businesses to maximize profitability and revenue growth from new and existing customers through marketing automation and enterprise-wide customer management. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>XTND</Symbol><Name>Extended Systems Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$69.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>1194</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, distributes, markets and sells connectivity products and mobile systems products, including virtual private networking server, internet access server, network print server and database management system with remote access capabilities and infrared software and port replicators which connect portable computers to desktop peripherals and the network.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FMBK</Symbol><Name>F &amp; M Bancorporation, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$548.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>43182</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking operations, mortgage banking, trust services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FYII</Symbol><Name>F.Y.I. Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$505.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>18104</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Provides document management services, including micrographic services, electronic imaging services, active storage and maintenance documents and files, archival storage of inactive documents, and information and database management services to healthcare institutions, professional services firms and financial institutions; Offers industry specific services such as litigation support, medical records release services and remittance processing; And sells micrographic and business imaging products.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RYFL</Symbol><Name>Family Steak Houses of Florida, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$3.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>89893</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Operates </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FARM</Symbol><Name>Farmer Brothers Company</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$319.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>84458</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Roasts, packages and distributes coffee and allied products to restaurants, hotels, hospitals, convenience stores and fast food outlets. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FCNBP</Symbol><Name>FCNB Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$239.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>58466</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FFWC</Symbol><Name>FFW Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$18.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>19634</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiaries which perform savings bank operations, mortgage banking, insurance services, investment banking services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ROMN</Symbol><Name>Film Roman, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$17.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>44121</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Creates, develops, produces and distributes high quality, family-oriented animated television programming; And licenses its proprietary characters to select manufacturers and distributors of consumer products such as toys, apparel, school supplies, housewares and books.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FISI</Symbol><Name>Financial Institutions, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$129.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>70047</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking operations, credit card services, trust services, leasing, mortgage banking and other related financial activities.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FSVP</Symbol><Name>FIND/SVP, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$5.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>17766</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops and markets a broad range of information services and products, such as custom research projects as well as publishing of copyrighted syndicated studies. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FCFN</Symbol><Name>First Community Financial Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>7573</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings and loan operations, mortgage banking and other related financial activities. new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FDEF</Symbol><Name>First Defiance Financial Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$83.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>19928</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiaries which perform savings bank operations, mortgage banking services, insurance services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FFBC</Symbol><Name>First Financial Bancorp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$888.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>37142</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Bank and savings and loan holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking operations, savings bank operations, credit card services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FFCH</Symbol><Name>First Financial Holdings, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$232.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>93712</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiaries which perform savings and loan operations and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FMAR</Symbol><Name>First Mariner Bancorp</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$31.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>12605</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiary which performs commercial banking operations, mortgage banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FSLA</Symbol><Name>First Sentinel Bancorp, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$348.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>23139</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which perform savings bank operations, mortgage banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FCLX</Symbol><Name>FirstCom Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$186.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>27375</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops and operates telecommunications systems in central and south america; And offers high speed data transmission services on a private line basis, including area network interconnection, remote terminal access dedicates channels for access to the internet and voice services on a private line basis.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FSRV</Symbol><Name>FirstService Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$159.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>37964</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide consumer services, such as landscape care, integrated security service with security officers and security systems; Offers property management and maintenance services, including lawn maintenance, irrigation, pest control, janitorial and various real estate services for condominium and homeowner associations; And offers franchise opportunities.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FLAS</Symbol><Name>FlashNet Communications, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$112.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>77272</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides internet access services, web hosting and co-location services, electronic commerce solutions and other value-added services.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FNBP</Symbol><Name>FNB Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$80.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>45566</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking operations and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>VIFL</Symbol><Name>Food Technology Service, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$44.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>5079</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Owns and operates irradiation facility which uses gamma radiation to treat or process various foods for insect disinfestation, shelf life extension and control of certain disease causing microorganisms. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FORR</Symbol><Name>Forrester Research, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$356.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>73891</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides analysis and insight into a broad range of technology areas such as computing, software, networking, the internet and telecommunications, projecting how technology trends will impact businesses, consumers and society. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>FELE</Symbol><Name>Franklin Electric Co., Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$384.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>58257</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and distributes electric motors, electronic controls and related equipment. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>EFTD</Symbol><Name>ftd.com, inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>69332</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Operates web site and toll-free telephone number, both of which market flowers and and specialty gifts, including stuffed animals and other plush toys, gourmet gift baskets, holiday gift sets and collectible containers. new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GALT</Symbol><Name>Galileo Technology Ltd.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,185.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>33754</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GELX</Symbol><Name>GelTex Pharmaceuticals, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$212.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>20592</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Develops non-absorbed, polymer-based pharmaceuticals which selectively bind to and eliminate target substances from the intestinal tract. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GDCOQ</Symbol><Name>Genesis Development and Construction, Ltd.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$11.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>77151</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GGNS</Symbol><Name>Genus, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$45.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>50314</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures, markets and services advanced thin film deposition, high energy ion implantation, and vapor phase wafer cleaning equipment for high-volume production of advanced ultra large scale integration semiconductor devices. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GEOI</Symbol><Name>GeoResources, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$5.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>97673</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Explores for, develops and produces oil and natural gas properties; And mines leonardite and manufactures leonardite based products which are sold primarily as oil and gas drilling mud additives.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GETY</Symbol><Name>Getty Images, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$832.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>9654</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Provides images which are used to communicate messages in a wide variety of applications, including print, electronic and broadcast advertising, direct mail and brochures, and educational and training publications. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GISH</Symbol><Name>Gish Biomedical, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$9.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>92336</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Designs, produces and markets innovative specialty surgical devices primarily blood handling and fluid delivery and blood management systems for cardiovascular surgery, oncology and orthopedics; And manufactures ambulatory infusion pumps.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GEMS</Symbol><Name>Glenayre Technologies, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$190.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>41312</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures, markets and services telecommunications equipment, such as switches, transmitters, receivers and controllers and related software used in the wireless personal communications service markets, including wireless messaging, voice processing, mobile data systems and point-to-point wireless interconnection products; And designs, develops and markets innovative, low-power, two-way paging devices.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GSPT</Symbol><Name>Global Sports, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$266.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>83552</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops and markets high performance athletic footwear for women, men and children; Purchases and resells a wide array of athletic, outdoor, casual and specialty footwear, athletic apparel, winter sports equipment, in-line skates, skateboards, and sunglasses; And designs and distributes special make-up snowboards and other sports-related merchandise for selected retailers.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GLDFY</Symbol><Name>Gold Fields of South Africa Limited</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$233.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>69845</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Explores for and mines gold and other precious metals. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GTIM</Symbol><Name>Good Times Restaurants Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$4.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>88888</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which develop, own, operate and franchise fast service restaurants under the name </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GATT</Symbol><Name>Grand Adventures Tour &amp; Travel Publishing Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$8.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>47680</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Publishes travel related magazine; Markets hotel/resort space to interline specializing in mexican and caribbean locations; And markets cruise and escorted tour packages to interliners.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GUCO</Symbol><Name>Grand Union Company (The)</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$406.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>44879</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Operates retail food stores offering a wide selection of national brand and private label grocery and general merchandise products as well as high-quality perishables and service departments. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GOJOW</Symbol><Name>GraphOn Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>90531</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GSLA</Symbol><Name>GS Financial Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$36.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>56625</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operations, mortgage banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GSLI</Symbol><Name>GSI Lumonics Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$115.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>13193</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, manufactures and markets laser-based advanced manufacturing systems for semiconductor, electronics, aerospace and automotive industries. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GWBK</Symbol><Name>Gulf West Banks, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$70.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>62296</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking operations, leasing, trust services, mortgage banking services, credit card services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GMRK</Symbol><Name>GulfMark Offshore, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$138.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>83607</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides offshore marine service to the energy industry with fleet of offshore supply vessels operating in the north sea and southeast asia to transport personnel, supplies, material and anchor handlers, and to move and position drilling structures of exploration and production of oil and gas properties.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GUMM</Symbol><Name>GumTech International, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$91.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>34124</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and distributes speciality chewing gum products under its own brand names and on private label basis. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HGGR</Symbol><Name>Haggar Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$91.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>15728</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures, imports and markets men's casual and dress apparel, including a wide variety of suits, sportcoats, shirts, pants and shorts. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HAMP</Symbol><Name>Hampshire Group, Limited</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$37.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>89835</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which manufacture and sell knitted sweaters; Acquire real estate properties and equity securities for investment purposes; And formerly manufactured and sold ladies' and children's hosiery and socks.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HDNG</Symbol><Name>Hardinge, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$150.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>69255</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and markets industrial-use and general precision turning machine tools; And offers extensive line of workholding and toolholding devices, and bar feed systems.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HFGI</Symbol><Name>Harrington Financial Group, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$24.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>82555</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiaries which perform savings bank operations, mortgage barking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HHFC</Symbol><Name>Harvest Home Financial Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$14.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>59891</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operations, mortgage banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HRVY</Symbol><Name>Harvey Entertainment Company</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$16.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>65029</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Owns and exploits a library of celebrated classic characters and other intellectual property assets, including a related film library of animated short features. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HWLD</Symbol><Name>Healthworld Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$103.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>52969</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide comprehensive range of integrated strategic marketing services, including advertising and promotion, contract sales, consulting, medical education, public relations, marketing research, publishing, interactive multimedia and database marketing services, designed to accelerate the market acceptance of new products and to sustain marketability throughout their life-cycles.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HERBA</Symbol><Name>Herbalife International, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$430.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>30753</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Markets weight management products, food and dietary supplements and personal care products worldwide. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HFWA</Symbol><Name>Heritage Financial Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$86.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>76388</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operations, mortgage banking services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IFITZ</Symbol><Name>Heuristic Development Group, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>90790</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HITK</Symbol><Name>Hi-Tech Pharmacal Co., Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$19.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>74506</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Manufactures over-the-counter pharmaceuticals, prescription drug products and nutritional preparations, primarily for the private label market. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HICKA</Symbol><Name>Hickok Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$8.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>35221</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures and markets automotive diagnostic systems, precision indicating instruments, fastening systems products and other electronic test equipments; Manufactures specialty pressure gauges for railroads and transit cars; And provides support services relating to the development of training curriculums for automotive technicians and others.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HTXA</Symbol><Name>Hitox Corporation of America</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$9.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>43322</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Manufactures and sells mineral products for use as pigments and extenders, primarily titanium dioxide used by manufacturers of paints, plastics and paper. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HMTT</Symbol><Name>HMT Technology Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$162.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>88509</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Manufactures and supplies thin film disks for high-end, high capacity hard disk drives used in high-end personal computers, network servers and workstations. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HOEN</Symbol><Name>Hoenig Group Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$94.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>45567</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide global stock brokerage, marketing, distribution of independent third party research, and professional investment management services to banks, insurance companies, corporations, employee benefit sponsors, investment advisors and other investment professionals.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HCFC</Symbol><Name>Home City Financial Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$11.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>63527</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operations, mortgage banking services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HGPI</Symbol><Name>Horizon Group Properties, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$10.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>18048</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Real estate investment trust which owns and manages factory outlet centers and a power center. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HDSN</Symbol><Name>Hudson Technologies, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$13.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>57232</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide refrigerant management services, consisting primarily of recovery and reclamation of refrigerants used in commercial air conditioning and refrigeration systems, and sell used and new regfrigerants. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HDIIU</Symbol><Name>Hypertension Diagnostics, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$9.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>77866</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IFLO</Symbol><Name>I-Flow Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$62.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>97835</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, manufactures and markets ambulatory infusion systems which administer antibiotics, analgesics, chemotherapeutic agents, hormones, nutrients, hydration therapies and other medical treatments to patients. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ISGTF</Symbol><Name>I.S.G. Technologies Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$51.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>29693</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures, markets and supports visual data processing technology for the medical imaging industry which display, manipulate and analyze two-and three-dimensional images of a patient's internal anatomy; And develops and markets imaging software, software platforms, software systems and related services to major medical equipment manufacturers and hospital systems integrators around the globe.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IATRW</Symbol><Name>IAT Resources Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>20746</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ICOCZ</Symbol><Name>ICO, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$16.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>40245</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide inspection, reconditioning and coating services for new and used tubular goods and sucker rods utilized in the oil and gas industry; And provides grinding, air milling and ancillary services for petrochemical resins produced in pellet form.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IICR</Symbol><Name>IIC Industries Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$56.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>62465</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which sell and distribute vehicles; Sell retail and wholesale consumer products; Export and import agricultural products; Trade agricultural, communications and electrical equipment; And distribute tractors and other heavy equipment.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IMMU</Symbol><Name>Immunomedics, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$54.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>85001</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Researches, develops, manufactures and sells medical products, particularly biological substances for use in cancer diagnosis, detection and therapy. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IMPX</Symbol><Name>IMP, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$6.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>42942</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops and manufactures application specific, standard integrated circuits and custom memory circuits; And provides silicon foundry services to fabless semiconductor manufacturers and other companies.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>INDB</Symbol><Name>Independent Bank Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$185.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>44004</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking operations, trust services, mortgage banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IBCPP</Symbol><Name>Independent Bank Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$15.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>60335</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking, operations, mortgage banking services, insurance services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>INDG</Symbol><Name>Indigo N.V.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$212.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>20340</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures, licenses, markets and services proprietary digital offset color printing systems, used in production of on-demand, short-run color printed products; And sells proprietary imaging products, including electronic products, photo-imaging plates, and image transfer blankets, essential to the operation of company's printing systems.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>INTI</Symbol><Name>Inet Technologies, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,674.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>74227</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides solutions that enable telecommunications carriers to more effectively design, deploy, diagnose, monitor and manage communications networks that carry signaling information used to manage telephone calls, addressing such business needs as improved billing, targeted sales and marketing, fraud prevention and enhanced call routing.  new registrant.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IMKTA</Symbol><Name>Ingles Markets, Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$290.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>94138</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Operates chain of retail supermarkets; Operates milk processing and packaging business; And owns shopping centers and other real estate outparcels.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>INHL</Symbol><Name>Inhale Therapeutic Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$457.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>3937</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Researches and develops pulmonary, non-invasive drug delivery system applicable to wide range of peptides, proteins and other macromolecules currently delivered by injection and other routes, including existing inhalation routes. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>INTO</Symbol><Name>Initio, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$6.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>87886</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiary which formerly provided mail order sales of consumer products, including leather outerwear, footwear, housewares, gifts, other apparel and accessories through mail order catalogs and space advertising. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>CMKG</Symbol><Name>Inmark Enterprises, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$12.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>43559</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops and implements customized, national, regional and local consumer and trade promotion programs principally for fortune five-hundred consumer product manufacturers and service providers. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>INOC</Symbol><Name>Innotrac Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$151.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>65125</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Provides customized, technology-based support services such as product and literature distribution, computerized inventory and database management. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IDEA</Symbol><Name>Innovasive Devices, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$67.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>5349</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, manufactures and markets proprietary tissue repair systems, including suture fasteners, suturing systems, cartilage repair and anterior cruciate ligament reconstruction products, which facilitate the repair of soft tissue injuries in either open surgical or minimally invasive arthroscopic procedures.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PURE</Symbol><Name>Innovative Medical Services</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$7.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>65502</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Manufactures, markets and sells proprietary pharmaceutical water purification and dispensing products. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>INSI</Symbol><Name>INSCI Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$32.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>85584</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and supports computer software systems which are designed to index, store and retrieve massive amounts of computer information; And offers software installation, training, software maintenance support and systems integration.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>INEI</Symbol><Name>Insituform East, Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$6.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>47110</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Repairs and rehabilitates underground sewers and pipelines, including waste water, storm water, and industrial process pipelines, using a novel technology. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IAAI</Symbol><Name>Insurance Auto Auctions, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$181.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>54843</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Purchases and auctions total loss and recovered theft vehicles; And offers insurance companies and other vehicle suppliers cost-effective salvage processing solutions, by auctioning on fixed fee consignment and percentage of sale consignment basis, various total loss and recovered theft vehicles.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IART</Symbol><Name>Integra LifeSciences Holdings Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$97.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>53679</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures and markets medical devices, implants and biomaterials primarily used in the treatment of burns and skin defects, spinal and cranial disorders, orthopedics and other surgical applications; And develops and sells absorbable medical products for drug delivery, surgical hemostasis, infection control, dental surgery and wound care applications.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>INTS</Symbol><Name>Integrated Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$242.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>34896</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, markets and supports software products and services enabling users to accelerate the design and implementation of control systems and the development of software for embedded microprocessors; Licenses its products; And offers engineering services to help customers implement specific solutions.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>INTC</Symbol><Name>Intel Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$254,509.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>18484</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, manufactures and markets advanced microcomputer components and related products at various levels of integration, such as silicon-based semiconductors etched with complex patterns of transistors, microprocessors and related board-level products, chipsets, embedded processors and microcontrollers, flash memory chips, network and communications products, and conferencing equipment, used to enhance the performance, capabilities and manageability of pc desktop and server systems in corporate networks.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>INTL</Symbol><Name>Inter-Tel, Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$433.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>80551</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Produces call processing and voice processing hardware and software, such as digital telephone systems, messaging software and voice processing software, along with various other productivity enhancing software applications; Provides computer telephone integration and network services, long distance calling services and related maintenance, leasing and support services; And resells other telecommunications products such as headsets, videoconferencing, surge protection and paging equipment.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>DENT</Symbol><Name>InterDent, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$172.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>44017</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides dental practice management and licensing services to multi-specialty dental practices, including billing and collection of patients receivables and administrative support services.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>INTXP</Symbol><Name>Interiors, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>57062</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Manufactures antique and contemporary picture frames for museums, art galleries, designers, collectors and frame retailers; Manufactures and markets a line of high-end traditional and contemporary mirrors through upscale retail furniture and department stores; And manufactures a variety of decorative accessories for the home.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ICIX</Symbol><Name>Intermedia Communications Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,088.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>55800</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Provides full suite of local, long distance and enhanced data telecommunications services to business and government customers, long distance carriers, internet service providers, resellers and wireless communications companies. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IFCI</Symbol><Name>International FiberCom, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$158.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>17379</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which design, install and maintain fiber-optic and other cable service for telecommunication and cable television industries; And sell and distribute new and used telecommunications equipment, including digital computer boards.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>INSS</Symbol><Name>International Network Services</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$3,108.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>95392</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Provides services for full life cycle of a network, including planning, design, implementation, operations and maintains expertise in complex network technologies and multivendor environments. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ISWIW</Symbol><Name>International Sports Wagering Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>36814</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>INTM</Symbol><Name>internet.com Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$288.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>32162</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Provides business-to-business vertical content web sites and related internet media properties, offering a wide variety of content, community and commerce products and services.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IPIC</Symbol><Name>Interneuron Pharmaceuticals, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$90.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>14533</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Researches, develops and commercializes innovative products for treating central nervous system, cardiovascular and other disorders, including multiple compounds in advanced-stage clinical development. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IWHM</Symbol><Name>Interwest Home Medical, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$13.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>73364</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiary which provides wide range of home health care services and products such as hospital beds, wheel chairs, rehabilitative equipment and services, respiratory therapy services, apnea monitors and enteral nutrition care. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IRIQE</Symbol><Name>Iridium World Communications Ltd.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$60.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>12116</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops and commercializes global mobile wireless communications systems which enable subscribers to send and receive telephone calls anywhere in the world. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ISKO</Symbol><Name>Isco, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$26.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>48811</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and markets a variety of instruments and equipment for use in scientific research and environmental pollution control monitoring. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SISG</Symbol><Name>ISG International Software Group Ltd.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$40.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>74956</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ITCD</Symbol><Name>ITC DeltaCom, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,566.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>61077</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides retail long distance services, including local exchange and long haul services to other telecommunications companies; And sells and services customer premise equipment.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ITII</Symbol><Name>ITI Technologies, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$237.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>67662</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and markets electronic security systems and access control systems. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ITLA</Symbol><Name>ITLA Capital Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$104.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>95652</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiaries which perform savings and loan operations, mortgage banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IYCOY</Symbol><Name>Ito-Yokado Co., Ltd.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$34,354.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>56709</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which operate chain of superstores which sell broad range of food, clothing and household goods; Operate and franchise convenience stores under the name </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IWRK</Symbol><Name>Iwerks Entertainment, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$10.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>68362</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Produces high-tech software-base theatre attractions products, offering ride simulation, giant screen, 360 degree, 3-d and various other specialty attractions for the out-of-home entertainment market; Owns and operates fleet of touring ride simulation theatres; Produces film and video software for ride simulators and special format theatres; Participates in joint ventures which own and operate ride simulation theatres; Rents large format cameras and related equipment; And provides certain post production services to large format film makers.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>JILL</Symbol><Name>J. Jill Group Inc. (The)</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$44.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>46582</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Markets broad assortment of women's apparel, accessories, shoes and gifts through full-color catalogs. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>JAMSO</Symbol><Name>Jameson Inns, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>51128</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>JAGI</Symbol><Name>Janus Hotels and Resorts, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$16.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>33521</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Owns and manages hospitality properties. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>JBOH</Symbol><Name>JB Oxford Holdings, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$115.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>89051</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiary which provides broker-dealer services, including discount brokerage, electronic trading and investment and merchant banking services. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>JMAR</Symbol><Name>JMAR Technologies, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$31.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>40348</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures and markets precision measurement, motion control and laser manufacturing systems; Provides custom semiconductor products for the microelectronics industry; And develops advanced lithography sources for the production of future higher performance semiconductors.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>JMARW</Symbol><Name>JMAR Technologies, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>94885</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>JWAIA</Symbol><Name>Johnson Worldwide Associates, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$72.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>66446</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Manufactures and markets recreational products for fishing, camping, underwater diving and marine activities such as tents, backpacks, canoes, tanks, masks, fins, rods, reels and other accessories. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>JMED</Symbol><Name>Jones Pharma Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,429.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>1549</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Manufactures and sells in both branded and generic form ethical drug products, non-prescription pharmaceuticals sold over-the-counter, and several vitamins and food supplement products. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>JUNI</Symbol><Name>Juniper Group, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$14.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>55168</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide cost containment services for third party healthcare payors through arrangements with preferred provider organizations and case management services; Offer revenue enhancement management services to hospitals; And distribute films through licensing to home video, pay-per-view, pay-cable and commercial television broadcast media.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>IWOV</Symbol><Name>Jupiter Communications, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>4395</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>KANA</Symbol><Name>Kana Communications, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>27463</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and supports software solutions that allow e-businesses to effectively manage web-based customer communications.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>KTTY</Symbol><Name>Kitty Hawk, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$174.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>31846</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides air freight carrier services; Scheduled freight services; Air logistics services; And engine overhaul and airframe repair services.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>KMGB</Symbol><Name>KMG Chemicals, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$44.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>49916</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Manufactures, markets and distributes wood preserving chemicals such as penta, creosote and chromated copper arsenate to industrial customers engaged in the wood preserving business. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>KOSP</Symbol><Name>Kos Pharmaceuticals, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$84.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>31309</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops proprietary prescription pharmaceutical products for treatment of certain chronic cardiovascular and respiratory diseases. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>KUAL</Symbol><Name>Kuala Healthcare Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$2.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>79491</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Operates long term care and assisted living facilities; Provides home health care services including enteral, parenteral nutrition and intravenous therapies; And markets, distributes and sells pharmaceuticals in russia.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BOOT</Symbol><Name>LaCrosse Footwear, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$36.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>87896</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, manufactures and markets premium quality protective footwear and rainwear, such as rubber/vinyl footwear, leather/fabric upper footwear, waterproof boots and breathable gore-tex/r/ booties in leather boots, for sporting, occupational and recreational markets; Manufactures footwear components and protective clothing; Operates factory outlet stores; And holds royalty interests in joint venture company.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LABN</Symbol><Name>Lake Ariel Bancorp, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$78.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>59816</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiary which performs commercial banking operations, leasing, insurance services and other related financail activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LKFNP</Symbol><Name>Lakeland Financial Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>60269</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LASE</Symbol><Name>LaserSight Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$243.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>48694</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures and markets ophthalmic lasers with galvanometric scanning systems primarily for use in performing photorefractive keratectomy; Provides health care and vision care consulting services to  hospitals, managed care companies and physicians; Licenses and owns patents related to keratome design and usage.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LSON</Symbol><Name>Lason, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$676.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>99893</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides integrated outsourcing services for records management, document management and business communications, including high-volume optical and digital printing, facility management operations at customer sites, converting inputs into digital formats, database management and direct mailing.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LCRY</Symbol><Name>LeCroy Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$131.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>45941</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures and sells signal analyzers, principally high-performance digital oscilloscopes and related products used by design engineers and researchers in a broad range of industries including electronics, computers and communications; And provides aftermarket support, repair, maintenance and recalibration of installed company products.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LVEL</Symbol><Name>Level 8 Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$110.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>37092</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide scalable enterprise application integration solutions through a combination of technologies and services which enable organizations to meet their information systems development, integration, management and e-commerce enablement needs, including scalable application integration and web-enablement tools, message-oriented middleware, and application development and management engines.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LGND</Symbol><Name>Ligand Pharmaceuticals Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$356.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>84723</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiary which discovers and develops small-molecule drugs which regulate gene activity and genetic processes in the treatment of certain cancers and other diseases. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LTBG</Symbol><Name>Lightbridge, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$399.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>35885</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and supports integrated software based products and services which enable wireless telecommunications carriers to improve their customer acquisition and retention processes; And offers on-line, real-time transaction processing and center support solutions to aid carriers in qualifying and activating applicants for wireless service, as well as software-based sales support services.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LPTHZ</Symbol><Name>LightPath Technologies, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$2.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>70448</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LNCR</Symbol><Name>Lincare Holdings Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,481.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>63446</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide oxygen and other respiratory services to patients in the home; And supply home medical equipment, such as hospital beds, wheelchairs and other supplies which may be required by patients.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LNET</Symbol><Name>LodgeNet Entertainment Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$156.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>26645</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides specialized communications services, serving the lodging industry in the united states and selected international markets. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LOAX</Symbol><Name>Log On America, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$156.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>65832</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides a full range of internet, voice, data and cable programming solutions.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LOGLF</Symbol><Name>Logal Educational Software &amp; Systems, Limited</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$2.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>88197</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LGASP</Symbol><Name>Louisville Gas and Electric Company</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$15.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>34424</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LEIX</Symbol><Name>Lowrance Electronics, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$27.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>35645</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and markets sonars and related equipment, such as water temperature gauges, and other navigational products, such as global positioning system receivers. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LXBK</Symbol><Name>LSB Bancshares, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$155.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>62400</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking operations, investment banking, trust services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MAGN</Symbol><Name>Magainin Pharmaceuticals Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$23.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>10000</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Develops medicines for serious diseases such as cancer by isolating and developing compounds from host-defense systems of animals and using molecular techniques to understand the pathogenesis of disease. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MGIC</Symbol><Name>Magic Software Enterprises Ltd</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$181.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>70836</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MAIN</Symbol><Name>Main Street and Main Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$12.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>8655</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Owns and operates franchises of casual dining restaurants under the name </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MANH</Symbol><Name>Manhattan Associates, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$102.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>53988</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Provides information technology solutions for distribution centers which are designed to enable the efficient movement of goods through the supply chain. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MTEX</Symbol><Name>Mannatech, Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$150.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>17576</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Develops and sells through network marketing system, proprietary nutritional supplements and topical products; And markets through network marketing system, products designed to aid in sports performance and nutritional support.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MANU</Symbol><Name>Manugistics Group, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$264.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>71934</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and supports line of operational planning and decision-making software products and services for supply chain management which is the process from raw materials procurement, through manufacturing and distribution to delivery of finished goods.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MATH</Symbol><Name>MathSoft, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$23.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>26016</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and supports software productivity tools for the technical calculation and data analysis markets comprised of professionals, research, students and educators; And provides technical support services.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MAXS</Symbol><Name>Maxwell Shoe Company Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$74.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>794</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, markets and sells moderately-priced casual and dress footwear for women, children and for other select retailers; And sells footwear closeouts purchased from other manufacturers.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MEDC</Symbol><Name>Med-Design Corporation (The)</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$34.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>21270</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs and develops safety medical devices, including retractable needle hypodermic syringe, retractable needle vacuum tube phlebotomy set and retractable needle intravenous catheter insertion device, intended to reduce the incidence of accidental needlesticks.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TAXI</Symbol><Name>Medallion Financial Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$283.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>45285</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MEDJ</Symbol><Name>Medi-Ject Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$4.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>15479</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures and markets needle-free injection systems for the self-administration of a wide range of parenteral drugs. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MEDI</Symbol><Name>MedImmune, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$6,521.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>12502</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Researches, develops, manufactures and markets therapeutics and vaccines for the treatment and prevention of certain infectious diseases and cancer, and for use in transplantation medicine. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MSCP</Symbol><Name>Medscape, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>65637</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Operates a healthcare web site which provides comprehensive, authoritative and timely medical information and interactive programs to physicians, allied healthcare professionals, such as pharmacists and nurses, and consumers.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MBWM</Symbol><Name>Mercantile Bank Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>62422</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiary which performs commercial banking operations and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MRBK</Symbol><Name>Mercantile Bankshares Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$2,237.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>32568</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking operations, mortgage banking, trust services, leasing, insurance services, investment advisory services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>KITS</Symbol><Name>Meridian Diagnostics, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$113.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>8793</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures and markets immunodiagnostic test kits, reagents and related products for use in physician offices and in hospital,  commercial and research laboratories. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MIGI</Symbol><Name>Meridian Insurance Group, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$120.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>50451</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which underwrite property and casualty insurance, including automobile, homeowners, farmowners and commercial multi-peril insurance. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MERX</Symbol><Name>Merix Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$89.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>47960</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Manufactures technologically advanced electronic interconnect solutions, including printed circuit boards, backplanes and flexible circuits used in sophisticated electronic equipment. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MCRE</Symbol><Name>MetaCreations Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$137.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>88146</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, publishes, markets and supports visual computing software tools and technologies for the creation, editing and manipulation of computer graphic images, digital art and internet/online content. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MMWW</Symbol><Name>Metamor Worldwide Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$557.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>71544</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide temporary and contract personnel to businesses, professional and service organizations, manufacturers, institutions, and government agencies; Provide computer professionals to staff programming, systems analysis, information technology consulting and other computer-related jobs; And offer specialized services such as technical communications outsourcing.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MEOH</Symbol><Name>Methanex Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$498.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>12917</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Produces and sells methanol at facilities in north america, new zealand and chile; And produces and sells limited amounts of gasoline.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MTLG</Symbol><Name>Metrologic Instruments, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$64.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>24309</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and markets bar code scanning equipment, including hand-held, fixed projection, in-counter and industrial scanners, which incorporate laser and holographic technology to accurately and efficiently read and decode all widely used bar codes.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MIKE</Symbol><Name>Michaels Stores, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$949.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>37517</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Operates specialty retail stores which provide a large assortment of general crafts, home decor items, picture framing materials and services, art and hobby supplies, party supplies, silk and dried flowers, wearable art, and seasonal and holiday merchandise.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MLIN</Symbol><Name>Micro Linear Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$49.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>46411</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops and markets high performance analog and mixed signal integrated circuits for application within the communications, computer and industrial markets. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MTIX</Symbol><Name>Micro Therapeutics, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$79.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>34076</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures and markets minimally invasive medical devices including a broad offering of infusion catheters, micro catheters and infusion wires, for the diagnosis and treatment of vascular disease. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MWHS</Symbol><Name>Micro Warehouse, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$436.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>36128</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Markets and retails brand name personal computers, computer software, accessories, peripherals and networking products to commercial and consumer customers, through mail order catalogs, telemarketing and the internet. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MCRS</Symbol><Name>MICROS Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$664.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>88519</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures, markets and services electronic point-of-sale and property management systems, related peripheral equipment and software for hospitality providers including full service and quick service restaurants, located in hotels and other lodging establishment, casinos, sports arenas, theme hotels, motels and resorts; And offers installation, training, hardware and software maintenance, parts, media supplies and consulting services.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MSEX</Symbol><Name>Middlesex Water Company</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$148.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>5976</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Collects, treats and distributes water for domestic, commercial, industrial and fire protection purposes in new jersey and delaware. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MLAN</Symbol><Name>Midland Company (The)</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$199.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>71860</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which specialize in writing physical damage insurance and related coverages on manufactured housing, watercraft, long-haul trucks, and commercial, excess and surplus lines; And provide barge chartering and freight brokerage services.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MSON</Symbol><Name>MISONIX, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$32.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>4961</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, manufactures and markets ultrasonic liquid processor and cell disruptors; Distributes other ultrasonic equipment for scientific and industrial purposes, including ductless fume enclosures for filtration of gaseous contaminants, scrubbers for the abatement of air pollution and ultrasonic spray nozzles and cleaners; And designs and develops surgical instruments.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MIND</Symbol><Name>Mitcham Industries, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$44.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>14926</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Leases and sells seismic data acquisition equipment to companies in the oil and gas industry, including channel boxes and other peripheral equipment. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MITSY</Symbol><Name>Mitsui &amp; Company, Ltd.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$11,590.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>46912</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Performs worldwide trading of various commodities, including arranging financing for customers and suppliers and organizing industrial projects on an international basis. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MORP</Symbol><Name>Moore Products Co.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$59.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>34470</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures, sells and supports industrial controls, instruments, dimensional measuring gauges and high-precision metrology calibration systems. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MFUN</Symbol><Name>Morgan FunShares, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>17171</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MOVA</Symbol><Name>Movado Group Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$311.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>9118</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and distributes quality watches, including exclusive watches made of precious metals and/or set with gems, luxury watches, premium branded watches and moderate branded watches. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>MNTG</Symbol><Name>MTR Gaming Group, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$71.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>9983</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which own and operate resort offering thoroughbred racing, simulcast off-track racing, video lottery gaming and outdoor activities; And owns limited oil and gas interests.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>LABL</Symbol><Name>Multi-Color Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$15.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>43828</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Produces printed in-mold labels for consumer products, such as liquid detergents, cigarettes, chewing gum and food products; Sells unprinted in-mold substrates to other label printing companies; And produces gift wrap.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>HITS</Symbol><Name>musicmaker.com, INC</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$293.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>4216</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Provides customized music cd compilations over the internet.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NTAI</Symbol><Name>Nam Tai Electronics, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$135.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>10201</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which design, develop, manufacture, assemble and sell calculators, personal organizers and linguistic products, and electronic components and subassemblies; Provide silk screening and circuit board assembly services for original equipment manufacturers; And develop integrated circuit smart card readers.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NCBM</Symbol><Name>National City Bancorporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$154.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>15471</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking operations, trust services, international banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NHHC</Symbol><Name>National Home Health Care Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$20.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>12204</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide personal home health care services to elderly, ill and infirm patients; Perform home intravenous infusion therapy; Operate and maintain out-patient medical offices offering multi-specialty and primary medical care; And provide administrative and non-medical management services.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NAVR</Symbol><Name>Navarre Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$234.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>8644</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Distributes home entertainment products including prerecorded tapes, compact discs and personal computer software; Publishes and distributes interactive cd-rom products; And owns and operates audio broadcaster on the internet.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NESY</Symbol><Name>NEON Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$258.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>58686</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Develops and sells software products which help organizations access and integrate data, transactions and applications from the internet and mainframe and client/server systems. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NWREW</Symbol><Name>Neoware Systems Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>57070</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NTIQ</Symbol><Name>NetIQ Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$112.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>93224</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Provides performance and availability management software for windows nt-based systems and applications.  new registraant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NSIL</Symbol><Name>NETsilicon, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$163.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>68761</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Develops and manufactures a networking system-on-silicon line of products designed to network-enable a broad array of electrical devices and makes it possible for those devices to be monitored and controlled from a remote location.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NASC</Symbol><Name>Network Access Solutions Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$601.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>9783</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Offers high speed channelized and packetized data communications services; And provides enterprise networking solutions, including network integration, network management, network security and professional services.  new registrant.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NEWZ</Symbol><Name>NewsEDGE Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$159.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>48316</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides customized, real-time news and information from a number of competitive sources to knowledge workers over their organizations' local area networks. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NCNT</Symbol><Name>Nichols TXEN Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>6956</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NOLD</Symbol><Name>Noland Company</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$74.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>50883</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Distributes plumbing, heating, air conditioning, electrical, and industrial supplies. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NCLIP</Symbol><Name>North Coast Life Insurance Company</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>31293</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TNFI</Symbol><Name>North Face, Inc. (The)</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$74.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>40377</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs and distributes high-performance, technically-oriented outerwear, skiwear, functional sportswear, tents, sleeping bags, backpacks, rock climbing shoes, mountaineering boots and other rugged footwear; And operates or owns retail stores, outlet stores and small, in-store, concept stores, which carry company's merchandise.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NFLD</Symbol><Name>Northfield Laboratories, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$192.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>73087</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, safe and effective alternatives to transfer blood for use in the treatment of acute blood loss, including </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NTFYU</Symbol><Name>Notify Technology Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$15.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>6511</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>NMTX</Symbol><Name>Novametrix Medical Systems Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$26.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>58654</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures, and markets medical electronic instruments and disposable products, such as non-invasive oxygen and carbon dioxide monitors and respiratory monitors. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>OAKT</Symbol><Name>Oak Technology, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$203.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>11982</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops and markets high performance multimedia semiconductors and related software to original equipment manufacturers which serve the multimedia personal computer, digital video consumer electronics and digital office equipment markets. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ODETA</Symbol><Name>Odetics, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$105.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>91909</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, manufactures and markets subsystems and other products for specialized information automation applications, including magnetic tape cartridge and cassette handling subsystems, large-library cart machines, time-lapse video cassette recorders and space-qualified digital data recorders.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ASGN</Symbol><Name>On Assignment, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$258.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>19638</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides temporary scientific professionals to laboratories in the biotechnology, environmental, chemical, food and beverage industries. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ONTC</Symbol><Name>ON Technology Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$64.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>37817</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and supports groupware applications and network management software, including client/server tools for group scheduling, group collaberation, electronic mail, software metering and server auditing. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ORCC</Symbol><Name>Online Resources &amp; Communications Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$13.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>10147</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Provides electronic commerce solutions which enable regional and community financial institutions to provide branded internet and other online banking services to their retail customers.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PLAN</Symbol><Name>Open Plan Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$10.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>47974</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Restores, remanufactures, manufactures and markets modular office work stations; And offers office furniture, such as simple desks, storage units and office chairs, from various manufacturers.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>OTEX</Symbol><Name>Open Text Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$466.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>5690</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets, licenses and supports an integrated product suite which combines enterprise document management, visual workflow and powerful searching in a web-based environment for project collaboration, accessed through standard web browsers. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>OPSI</Symbol><Name>Optical Sensors Incorporated</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$8.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>12124</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures and markets fiberoptic chemical sensors for blood gas monitoring for medically unstable patients in critical and intensive care units. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>OPTN</Symbol><Name>OPTION CARE, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$40.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>90687</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Provides full-service home health care, offering home infusion therapy, home health nursing, respiratory therapy, durable medical equipment and other home health services; Franchises outpatient health centers; And supplies state of the art data management products and services to the home health industry.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ORBK</Symbol><Name>Orbotech Ltd.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$850.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>26624</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ORCT</Symbol><Name>Orckit Communications, Limited</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$495.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>97273</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>GOSHA</Symbol><Name>Oshkosh B'Gosh, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$325.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>88368</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and markets broad range of children's clothing, youth wear and men's casual and work wear clothing; And offers children's footwear collection.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>OSIS</Symbol><Name>OSI Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$31.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>82911</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and provides optoelectronic devices, value-added subsystems and end-products for oems for use in broad range of applications, including security, medical diagnostics, telecommunications, office automation, aerospace, computer peripherals and industrial automation.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ICED</Symbol><Name>Packaged Ice, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$54.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>20014</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Manufactures and distributes packaged ice and bottled water; Owns and operates refrigerated warehouses; And manufactures and leases ice production equipment.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PBCI</Symbol><Name>Pamrapo Bancorp, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$62.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>39893</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operations, mortgage banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PNRA</Symbol><Name>Panera Bread Company</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$86.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>46760</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Operates and franchises bakery cafes under the name </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PTHW</Symbol><Name>Pathways Group, Inc. (The)</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$71.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>77002</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, markets and services custom smart card applications; And manufactures and markets automated ticketing kiosks.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PFCO</Symbol><Name>PAULA Financial</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$38.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>18795</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which underwrite and distribute commercial insurance products, such as worker's compensation insurance products and services for the agribusiness industry; And offer life and health insurance, third party administration, managed care programs, property and casualty insurance, crop insurance, life and disability insurance and other financial services.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PMRTZ</Symbol><Name>PawnMart, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>60797</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PCDI</Symbol><Name>PCD Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$71.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>71699</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and markets electronic connectors used in virtually all electronic systems, including data communications, telecommunications, computers and computer peripherals, industrial controls, automotive, avionics and test and measurement instrumentation.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PSAI</Symbol><Name>Pediatric Services of America, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$7.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>66792</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides comprehensive pediatric home health care services to children, respiratory and infusion therapy and other services to adults, delivery and setup of respiratory equipments, such as ventilators, apnea monitors and aerosol generators, evaluation and maintenance of such equipments, delivery and setup of supplies necessary for the operation of such equipments, rentals and service of home medical equipments, which consist of wheelchairs, beds, walkers and other equipments, and comprehensive medical and paramedical testing such as health histories, phlebotomy services and electrocardiograms to life, health and disability insurance companies.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PBCT</Symbol><Name>People's Bank</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,503.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>63696</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Performs savings bank operations, mortgage banking services, credit card services, investment banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PSTI</Symbol><Name>Per-Se Technologies, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$256.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>35863</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides billing, accounts receivable and other business management services to hospital affiliated physicians; And provides application software and a broad range of information technology and consulting services to healthcare and other service-oriented markets.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PHEL</Symbol><Name>Petroleum Helicopters, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$33.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>71529</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Transports personnel, and to a lesser extent parts and equipment, to, from and among offshore oil and gas platforms; And owns and operates radio communications flight network.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PHELK</Symbol><Name>Petroleum Helicopters, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$50.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>85214</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Transports personnel, and to a lesser extent parts and equipment, to, from and among offshore oil and gas platforms; And owns and operates radio communications flight network.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PHLY</Symbol><Name>Philadelphia Consolidated Holding Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$186.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>69482</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which design, market, and underwrite specialized commercial property and casualty insurance primarily for rental car companies and their customers, automotive leasing companies and their customers, and non-profit organizations.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PGDA</Symbol><Name>Piercing Pagoda, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$116.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>87689</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Operates specialty jewelry kiosk stores and in-line stores which offer popular-priced gold earings, chains, charms, bracelets and rings, as well as silver jewelry. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PCLE</Symbol><Name>Pinnacle Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$951.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>34074</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and markets high performance, cost-effective video workstations, which perform a variety of video post-production functions, including the addition of special effects, graphics, titles and 3-d images. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PRRR</Symbol><Name>Pioneer Railcorp</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$8.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>53798</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide railroad transportation services, such as shipping links for customers along its routes and interchanges with major railroads; Grant to various entities, including utilities, pipeline and communications companies, right to occupy its railroad right of way and other real estate property; And purchase, sell, lease and repair equipment to unrelated parties.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PHFCP</Symbol><Name>Pittsburgh Home Financial Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>79998</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PBYP</Symbol><Name>Play By Play Toys &amp; Novelties, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$28.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>59</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, markets and distributes stuffed toys and sculpted toy pillows; And markets and distributes broad line of novelty items.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PLXT</Symbol><Name>PLX Technology, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$462.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>69705</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops and markets input/ouput interconnectivity solutions which accelerate and manage the transfer of data in high-performance embedded systems, including semiconductor devices, as well as related software development kits and reference design kits.  new registrant.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>POPEZ</Symbol><Name>Pope Resources</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$141.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>85694</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>POPM</Symbol><Name>PopMail.com Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$14.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>61587</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Develops, owns and operates theme restaurants with a retail component, designed to appeal to the upscale dining market. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>POPMU</Symbol><Name>PopMail.com Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$11.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>95231</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PRSF</Symbol><Name>Portal Software, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$4,073.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>99490</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and supports customer management and billing software designed to meet the complex, mission-critical provisioning, accounting, reporting, marketing needs of providers of internet-based services.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PPTV</Symbol><Name>PPT Vision Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$17.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>76259</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and markets integrated machine-vision based automated inspection systems for manufacturing applications such as electronic and mechanical assembly verification, character verification, packaging integrity, surface flaw detection and gauging and measurement tasks.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PBSI</Symbol><Name>Precept Business Services, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$31.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>68082</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Distributes custom and stock business products and provider of document management services to businesses of all sizes throughout the united states. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>POCI</Symbol><Name>Precision Optics Corporation, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$7.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>28460</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and sells specialized optical systems and components for medical and industrial applications, and optical thin film coatings for industrial and government applications. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PSRC</Symbol><Name>PrimeSource Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$38.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>12686</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Distributes printing and imaging supplies including film, plates and proofing and photographic chemicals; Distributes high-technology electronic equipment, printing presses and bindery equipment; And provides system design, installation, servicing, training and technical support as well as ongoing workflow and cost-support analyses to the digital electronic component market.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PRCT</Symbol><Name>Procept, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$21.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>56184</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Develops and markets proprietary therapeutic compounds to treat disorders of the immune system. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PRGY</Symbol><Name>Prodigy Communications Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,006.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>18033</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Provides internet access and related value-added services. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TRUC</Symbol><Name>Professional Transportation Group Ltd., Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$4.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>19133</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide ground transportation  and logistics services of a time-sensitive nature to air freight and floorcovering industry, offering both local and long distance trucking with precise pickup and delivery schedules; Broker truckload services to air freight industry; And operate courier/delivery service which retrieves and returns copiers, fax machines, and telephone equipment, in the atlanta, georgia metropolitan area.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>POVT</Symbol><Name>Provant, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$278.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>48686</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Provides training and development services and products designed to increase the productivity of organizations by improving employee selection, recruitment and retention, enhancing employee work skills, and developing management and leadership skills, to large and medium-sized corporations and government entities.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PXCM</Symbol><Name>Proxicom, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,271.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>11001</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides internet solutions, including business to consumer electronic commerce internet sites, business to business electronic commerce extranets and company-specific intranets.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PSSI</Symbol><Name>PSS World Medical Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$594.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>43376</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which distribute medical supplies, equipment and pharmaceuticals to primary care and other office-based physicians. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PULB</Symbol><Name>Pulaski Financial Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$41.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>88120</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operation, mortgage banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PVFC</Symbol><Name>PVF Capital Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$60.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>75976</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operations, mortgage banking services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>QEKG</Symbol><Name>Q-Med, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$39.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>34859</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures, markets and sells advanced electronic monitors for cardiac and related applications, including ambulatory and portable computerized electrocardiographic (ecg) monitors; And manufactures and markets other non-invasive medical devices.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>QSYS</Symbol><Name>Quad Systems Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$7.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>40826</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures, markets and supports high accuracy surface mount assembly equipment used to manufacture printed circuit boards in low to medium volume production environments; Provides component feeders, machine vision systems; Offers turnkey systems incorporating an assembly system and a reflow oven; And formerly manufactured screen printers.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>QMRK</Symbol><Name>QualMark Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$8.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>7820</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and markets proprietary systems which rapidly and efficiently expose product design and manufacturing-related defects for the purpose of improving product quality and reliability; And operates network of test centers which provide test and support services to electronics, testing and communication industries.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>QSRI</Symbol><Name>Queen Sand Resources, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$14.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>12089</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Explores for, develops, acquires and sells crude oil and natural gas. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RDCM</Symbol><Name>RADCOM LTD.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$40.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>84393</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RAWL</Symbol><Name>Rawlings Sporting Goods Company, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$68.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>73784</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Madison</City></Address><Description>Supplies sports equipment, including uniforms, protective gear and various accessories; And licenses the use of </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RCMT</Symbol><Name>RCM Technologies, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$106.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>3370</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides temporary and contract personnel to businesses, professional and service organizations, manufacturers and public utilities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RLAXY</Symbol><Name>Realax Software AG</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>43360</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets and supports virtual reality software and solutions for commercial applications. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RESY</Symbol><Name>Reconditioned Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>41098</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Reconditions, markets and sells modular office work stations consisting of panels, work surfaces, file drawers, book and binder storage, and integrated electrical components. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RCOT</Symbol><Name>Recoton Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$83.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>3237</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Manufactures and markets a comprehensive line of accessories for consumer electronics equipment, including antennas, stereo headphones, loudspeakers, remote controls, audio and video tapes, cellular batteries, computer accessories, video and computer games and other accessories.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RHAT</Symbol><Name>Red Hat, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$6,073.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>42408</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Develops and provides open source software products and services; And maintains a web site which provides information and news about open source software and offers software downloads.  new registrant.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>REMC</Symbol><Name>REMEC, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$313.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>96592</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs and manufactures microwave multi-function modules for microwave transmission systems used in defense applications and the commercial wireless telecommunications market; And designs and manufactures precision instruments for guidance, control and measurement systems used by the defense, aerospace, petroleum and mining industries.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RENN</Symbol><Name>Renaissance Capital Growth &amp; Income Fund III, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$39.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>29649</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RENX</Symbol><Name>Renex Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$29.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>30915</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide dialysis and ancillary services through outpatient dialysis facilities, inpatient services at hospitals, and staff-assisted home dialysis programs, to patients suffering from chronic kidney failure. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RBMG</Symbol><Name>Resource Bancshares Mortgage Group, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$130.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>84123</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Purchases, originates and sells mortgage loans primarily to institutional purchasers; Originates, sells and services small-ticket commercial equipment leases; And originates, sells, underwrites for investors and services commercial mortgage loans.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>REXL</Symbol><Name>Rexhall Industries, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$27.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>92522</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and sells self-contained and self-powered motorhomes and recreational vehicles used primarily in conjunction with leisure travel and outdoor activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RFMI</Symbol><Name>RF Monolithics, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$59.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>39859</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures and markets broad range of radio frequency components and modules, such as resonators, filters and delay lines, for low-power wireless, high-frequency timing and telecommunications markets. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RTST</Symbol><Name>Right Start, Inc. (The)</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$51.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>73842</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Sells broad selection of high quality products for infant, toddler and preschool children through a catalog and retail stores. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RNIC</Symbol><Name>Robinson Nugent, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$24.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>51309</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and markets electronic devices, such as integrated circuit sockets, connectors and custom molded-on cable assemblies used to interconnect components of electronic systems; Offers application tooling for applying wire and cable; And provides engineering assistance, product design and manufacturing of custom and derivative products.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ROBV</Symbol><Name>Robotic Vision Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$116.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>96751</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures, markets and installs machine vision-based products, including semiconductor lead inspection systems and printed circuit board solder quality control products for productivity improvement and quality control applications in the manufacturing workplace; And develops and markets ice detection product for the aviation industry.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ROHN</Symbol><Name>ROHN Industries Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$106.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>40486</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Manufactures and installs wireless infrastructure products for the communications industry, including towers, equipment enclosures, steel and concrete poles, concrete and fiberglass equipment enclosures, equipment cabinets and antenna mounts; And manufactures galvanized steel agriculture products, including horse stalls, cattle equipment, fencing and gates.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ROCLF</Symbol><Name>Royal Olympic Cruise Lines, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$40.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>6977</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Operates fleet of overnight cruise ships in the mediterranean, offering destination-oriented cruises to sites of historical and cultural significance, combined with high standards of accommodation and passenger service. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ROME</Symbol><Name>Rudolph Technologies, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>47913</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>RFGI</Symbol><Name>Rushmore Financial Group, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$11.3</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>5276</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide a wide range of investment and insurance services and products, including securities brokerage services, mutual fund distribution, variable life insurance and annuities sales, and fee-based advisory services, to clients.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SNDK</Symbol><Name>SanDisk Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,687.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>14476</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops and markets flash memory data storage products used in a wide variety of electronic systems including desktop computers. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SAPE</Symbol><Name>Sapient Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$2,649.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>90225</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Performs innovative e-services consulting, through the delivery of integrated services, from business strategy and organizational transformation consulting, through user-centered design and technology implementation, assisting emerging and evolving businesses in transforing themselves into e-businesses.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SCNYA</Symbol><Name>Saucony, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$71.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>73063</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops and manufactures a broad line of athletic footwear, including running, women's walking, cross training, outdoor trail shoes as well as shoes for coaches and officials, high-quality bicycles and bicycle frames and performance athletic apparel.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SBEI</Symbol><Name>SBE, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$10.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>20674</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Develops, markets, sells and supports remote access internetworking products and high speed intelligent computer communications controllers which enable users to exchange data between computer systems. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SBTV</Symbol><Name>SBS Broadcasting SA</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$518.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>90965</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Owns and operates television and radio broadcasting stations in scandinavia and other european markets. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SCHR</Symbol><Name>Scherer Healthcare, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$14.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>95092</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which perform medical waste management services. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>BUNZ</Symbol><Name>Schlotzsky's, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$57.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>69265</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Owns, operates and franchises </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SCMM</Symbol><Name>SCM Microsystems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$659.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>9587</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops and manufactures standards-compliant hardware, firmware and software products and technologies used in smart card and other token-based network security and conditional access systems. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SHOE</Symbol><Name>Shoe Pavilion, Inc</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$24.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>5751</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Operates independent footwear retail stores on the west coast which fooers a broad selection of women's and men's designer label and name brand merchandise. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SIHS</Symbol><Name>SI Handling Systems, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$29.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>34999</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures, sells and installs mechanized and automated materials handling systems, including flexible conveyor system, automated order selection system and computer-controlled tilt-tray sortation system; And develops and designs computer control programs for its systems.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SCRI</Symbol><Name>SICOR, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$324.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>15943</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops proprietary cardiovascular products; And develops, manufactures and markets generic injectable drugs.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SILK</Symbol><Name>Silknet Software, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$978.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>73474</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides software which allows companies to offer personalized marketing, sales, electronic commerce and customer support services through a single company-tailored web site interface.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SFNCA</Symbol><Name>Simmons First National Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$195.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>58860</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking operations, mortgage banking services, credit card services, trust services, investment banking services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SSCC</Symbol><Name>Smurfit-Stone Container Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$4,277.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>59036</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which produce paperboard/packaging products including virgin and recycled containerboard, coated and uncoated recycled boxboard and solid bleached sulfate and recycled cylinderboard, and consumer packaging such as flexible packaging, paper and metallized paper labels and labels which are heat transferred to plastic containers for a wide range of industrial and consumer products applications; Produce full line containerboard including unbleached kraft linerboard, mottled white linerboard and recycled medium; Provide marketing consultation and research activities such as graphic and product design, rotogravure and flexographic printing, and photography for packaging, sales promotion concepts, and point of purchase displays; And formerly operated newsprint mills which produce and recycle newsprint.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SSPE</Symbol><Name>Software Spectrum, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$57.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>93884</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Resells business software for microcomputers; And offers business software technical services.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SOMN</Symbol><Name>Somnus Medical Technologies, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$32.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>57675</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, manufactures and markets innovative medical devices utilizing radio frequency technology, for the treatment of upper airway disorders. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SORC</Symbol><Name>Source Information Management Company (The)</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$233.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>71444</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Provides monitoring, documentation and collection services required to obtain single copy magazine sales incentive payments available from magazine publishers to retailers; And designs and manufactures displays and display racks for stores and retail checkout counters.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SCCB</Symbol><Name>South Carolina Community Bancshares, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$7.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>22606</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operations, mortgage banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SJFC</Symbol><Name>South Jersey Financial Corporation, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$50.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>2882</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings and loan operations, mortgage banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SBAN</Symbol><Name>SouthBanc Shares, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$69.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>11001</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operations, mortgage banking services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>STBF</Symbol><Name>Southeastern Thrift and Bank Fund, Inc. (The)</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$71.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>96846</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SMBC</Symbol><Name>Southern Missouri Bancorp, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$17.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>74810</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operations, mortgage banking services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SSLI</Symbol><Name>Southern Security Life Insurance Company</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$8.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>8891</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Underwrites universal life policies with various companion riders as well as traditional life products. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SBSI</Symbol><Name>Southside Bancshares, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$85.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>27353</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiaries which perform commercial banking operations, mortgage banking, credit card services, investment banking services, trust services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SMCX</Symbol><Name>Special Metals Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$60.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>6613</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Provides superalloy and special alloy long products designed to withstand extreme heat and stress, principally used in the manufacture of jet engine parts; And produces superalloy powders and amalgamable dental alloys.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SPRX</Symbol><Name>Spectrx, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$71.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>41525</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Researches and develops products which offer less invasive and painless alternatives to blood tests currently used for glucose monitoring, diabetes screening, infant jaundice and cancer detection. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SPCH</Symbol><Name>Sport Chalet, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$28.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>15655</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Operates sporting goods superstores which sell sporting goods merchandise and nontraditional merchandise, such as downhill skiing, cycling, mountaineering, scuba and ocean kayaking apparel and equipment. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SMCS</Symbol><Name>Star Multi Care Services, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$6.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>18858</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Provides registered and licensed nurses and home health aides to patients for care at home and to a lesser extent temporary health care personnel recruiting to hospitals and nursing homes. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>STNV</Symbol><Name>Statia Terminals Group N.V.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$88.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>18706</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Owns and operates marine terminal companies which handles crude oil storage.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>STHLY</Symbol><Name>STET Hellas Telecommunications S.A.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$1,442.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>97124</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Provides mobile telecommunications services in greece; Operates retail stores which offer mobile handsets as well as customer service and billing services; And offers network communications services, including the lease of lines that transmit voice and data traffic between a customer's sites.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>STLBY</Symbol><Name>Stolt-Nielsen S.A. c/o Stolt-Nielsen S.A.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$933.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>63959</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which transport, store and distribute bulk liquid chemicals, edible oils, acids and other specialty liquids; Conduct subsea construction and engineering services to offshore oil and gas and aquaculture industries; And produce and market high quality seafood products including atlantic salmon, salmon trout, turbot and halibut.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>STRS</Symbol><Name>Stratus Properties, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND00</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$60.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>16680</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Acquires and develops real estate properties such as residential, multi-family and commercial properties. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>STRA</Symbol><Name>Strayer Education, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$222.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>36261</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which offer accredited undergraduate and graduate degree programs, primarily to working adults pursuing a higher education on a part-time basis, in washington, d.c., maryland and northern virginia; And purchase, service and administer student loans, principally for the company's university.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>STYL</Symbol><Name>Styling Technology Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$40.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>99552</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Develops, produces and markets high-end professional salon products including hair care, nail care, and skin and body care products as well as salon appliances and salonwear. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SBGA</Symbol><Name>Summit Bank Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$23.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>79639</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiary which performs commercial banking operations, mortgage banking services, credit card services, international banking services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SUNP</Symbol><Name>SunPharm Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$11.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>91421</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Develops small molecule pharmaceutical products for the treatment of acquired immunodeficiency syndrome, gastrointestinal disorders and cancer. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SRDX</Symbol><Name>SurModics, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$112.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>16606</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides high value-added surface modification solutions including interventional cardiology catheters, vascular stents, interventional neurology catheters, guide wires and shunts, cardiac rhythm management devices, and urological and gynecological devices to a variety of medical device markets and product categories.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SYBB</Symbol><Name>SYNSORB Biotech Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$58.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>31067</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Discovers and develops pharmaceutical products for gastroenteric diseases or conditions which could benefit from alternative therapies or for which therapies are unavailable or existing therapies are inadequate. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TAMRW</Symbol><Name>TAM Restaurants, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>90711</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TPARY</Symbol><Name>Telepartner A/S</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$26.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>91286</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TTEC</Symbol><Name>TeleTech Holdings, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$828.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>84032</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides customer care solutions, including customer acquisition, retention and satisfaction programs, primarily through customer-initiated telephone calls and also over the internet, for large and multinational companies. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>WRLS</Symbol><Name>Telular Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$16.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>39725</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, develops, manufactures and markets products based on proprietary interface technology, which provides capability to bridge wireline telecommunications customer premises equipment with cellular-type transceivers for use in wireless communication networks, whether cellular or satellite based.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TANT</Symbol><Name>Tennant Company</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$304.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>76218</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures and sells sweepers, scrubbers and other specialized industrial and commercial floor maintenance equipment and related products. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>WATR</Symbol><Name>Tetra Tech, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$616.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>36742</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides comprehensive environmental engineering and consulting services addressing complex water contamination and other environmental problems, as well as infrastructure and telecommunications services. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TRBS</Symbol><Name>Texas Regional Bancshares, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$362.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>72322</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiary which performs commercial banking operations, mortgage banking, trust services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TACX</Symbol><Name>The A Consulting Team, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$28.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>83953</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides enterprise-wide information technology consulting, software and training services and solutions to fortune 1000 companies in a wide range of industries. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ARTL</Symbol><Name>The Aristotle Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$6.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>62408</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Seeks potential business opportunities; And formerly manufactured women's intimate apparel including specialty brassieres and shapewear products.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>EBSC</Symbol><Name>The Elder-Beerman Stores Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$91.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>21211</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>WI</State><City>Milwalkee</City></Address><Description>Operates independent department stores offering moderate to better branded merchandise, including women's ready-to-wear, men's and children's apparel, acessories, shoes and cosmetics, home furnishings and other consumer goods; And owns and operates a private label credit card program.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>PRED</Symbol><Name>The Orlando Predators Entertainment, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$14.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>25261</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Owns and operates the </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TUNZ</Symbol><Name>The TriZetto Group, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND06</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>4443</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>THTL</Symbol><Name>Thistle Group Holdings, Co.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$59.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>74578</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings bank operations, mortgage banking and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TIER</Symbol><Name>Tier Technologies, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$79.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>71563</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Provides information technology consulting, application development and software engineering services which facilitate the migration of clients' enterprise-wide systems and applications to leading edge technologies. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TEXP</Symbol><Name>Titan Exploration, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$182.6</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>78776</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiary which explores for, acquires and develops oil and natural gas properties primarily in the permian basin of west texas and southeastern new mexico, the gulf coast region and the gulf of mexico. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TENT</Symbol><Name>Total Entertainment Restaurant Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$16.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>3265</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Owns and operates entertainment restaurants with full menu and full service bar, state-of-the-art audio and video systems for sports entertainment, traditional games of skill such as pocket billiards, and late-night dining. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TELU</Symbol><Name>Total-Tel USA Communications, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND04</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$103.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>65520</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which provide long distance telephone communications services. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TOWR</Symbol><Name>Tower Air, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$28.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>35090</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides primarily long-haul scheduled and charter passenger air services in domestic, military and international markets; And provides third party maintenance services at its facilities.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TRAC</Symbol><Name>Track Data Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$128.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>81231</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Provides electronically transmitted financial information, including real-time financial market data, financial data bases, historical information, analytical services and manipulation tools through a sophisticated private data network to high end users in the equity/options/futures trading marketplaces; And develops and markets financial investment software for individual and professional users.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TRFWF</Symbol><Name>Tramford International, Ltd. c/o Jing Tai Industrial Inv.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>79162</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TGBR</Symbol><Name>Trans-Global Interactive Limited ADR</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>4459</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Explores for and develops mineral prospects, including copper and gold. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TRMS</Symbol><Name>Trimeris, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$203.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>8723</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Diego</City></Address><Description>Discovers and develops novel therapeutic agents which block viral infection by inhibiting viral fusion with host cells. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TRYF</Symbol><Name>Troy Financial Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$130.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>73273</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Savings and loan holding company with subsidiary which performs savings and loan operations, trust services, investment banking and other related financial activities.  new registrant. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TCNJ</Symbol><Name>Trust Company of New Jersey (The)</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$438.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>45242</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Performs savings bank operations and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>TWLB</Symbol><Name>Twinlab Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$295.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>36886</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Manufactures and markets nutritional supplements, such as vitamins, minerals, amino acids, fish and mineral oils, sports nutrition products, herbal supplements, herb teas and nutritionally enhanced food bars. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>USEG</Symbol><Name>U.S. Energy Corp.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND03</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$34.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>12129</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Acquires, explores for, develops and sells mineral properties containing uranium, gold and molybdenum; Owns and operates a motel and rental real estate; Performs aircraft fuel sales, flight instruction and aircraft maintenance; Constructs irrigation, flood control, municipal sewers and other similar projects; And explores for and develops oil and natural gas properties in montana and wyoming.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>USPN</Symbol><Name>U.S. Pawn, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$5.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>16264</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Operates pawnshops which lend money on security of pledged tangible personal property; And sells new and used goods.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>USVI</Symbol><Name>U.S. Vision, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$31.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>15740</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Operates retail vision care stores which offer prescription eyewear, lenses, sunglasses and accessories with an on-premises, independent optometrist who performs complete eye examinations and prescribes eyeglasses and contact lenses. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>XPRSA</Symbol><Name>U.S. Xpress Enterprises, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$89.5</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>27888</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Performs time-definite truckload transportation services, including expedited delivery services, and contract logistics management and information services, in the united states, canada and mexico. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>ULBI</Symbol><Name>Ultralife Batteries, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$42.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>71939</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>San Francisco</City></Address><Description>Develops, manufactures and markets lithium batteries for use in applications requiring high energy, reliable and long-lasting power sources; Develops rechargeable lithium-ion solid-polymer battery; Produces silver-chloride sea water batteries; And provides research and development services to government agencies and other third parties pursuant to technology contracts.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>UNNL</Symbol><Name>Union National Bancorp, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>94712</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Bank holding company with subsidiary which performs commercial banking operations, investment banking services, trust services and other related financial activities. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>UNSRA</Symbol><Name>Uniservice Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$5.7</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>25334</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company which owns and operates restaurants under the </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>UPUP</Symbol><Name>United Payors &amp; United Providers, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND01</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$290.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>76361</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Operates provider network consisting of hospitals, ancillary health care facilities and physicians, which offers health care beneficiaries of payor clients access to cost effective health care services nationwide or in particular geographic regions. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>URGI</Symbol><Name>United Retail Group, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$133.1</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>98083</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Operates retail stores which offer large-size women's apparel and accessories including casualwear, career apparel and specialty items. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>USLM</Symbol><Name>United States Lime &amp; Minerals, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND02</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$24.4</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>79927</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which extract and process raw limestone for sale as aggregate, pulverized limestone, quicklime and hydrated lime. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>UTGI</Symbol><Name>United Trust Group, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$15.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>29869</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which underwrite universal life insurance products. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>UVEW</Symbol><Name>uniView Technologies Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND05</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$22.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>63957</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Holding company with subsidiaries which deliver end-to-end convergence technology for a variety of niche set top box applications; And provide system integration, technical support and network consulting.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>SPEIG</Symbol><Name>USA Networks, Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$0.0</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>39864</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Not Available</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>VNTV</Symbol><Name>Vantive Corporation (The)</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND07</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$225.2</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>81437</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Designs, markets and supports software suite which enables businesses to enhance customer satisfaction by automating sales, marketing, call centers, field services, help desk and quality assurance operations. </Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>VCMP</Symbol><Name>VCampus Corporation</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND08</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$13.9</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>5626</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>XY</State><City>ZW</City></Address><Description>Publishes high-quality, interactive and on-demand educational courseware for on-line educational and training markets; And offers educational and training courseware through traditional media, including on-site and classroom training, and diskette, cd-rom and printed formats.</Description></Profile></Company>
<Company><Symbol>VECO</Symbol><Name>Veeco Instruments Inc.</Name><Sector>SEC0</Sector><Industry>IND09</Industry><Profile><MarketCap>$445.8</MarketCap><EmployeeNumber>34690</EmployeeNumber><Address><State>CA</State><City>Los Angelus</City></Address><Description>Designs, manufactures, markets and services broad line of precision ion beam etching and surface measurement systems used to manufacture microelectronic products for the data storage and semiconductor industries. </Description></Profile></Company>
</Companies>
